

Front-End Devloper

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- Java Script
- SQI
- React
- Npm
- Git/Github
- TailwindCSS

Soft Skill

- Creative
- Good Communication
- Hard Working
- Problem Solving

Contact

- **(S)** +(964) 750 116 9342
- sanarizgar34@gmail.com
- O Sulaymaniah,KRI-Iraq

Account

- pithub.com/Sanaa00
- **6** Sana Rizgar

About

I'm Sana Rzgar Latif , Software Engineer & Front-End developer, I have been in Graphic Design field for several years ,I try to use my technical skills with dedication & sincerity for the benefit of company and to achieve new heights in my career

Education

2020-2021 Bachelor Degre

Salahaddin University - College of Engineering Software & Informatics Department

2021 Certification

Freelance mentorship program

2022 Certification

Front-End web development bootcamp (3 months)

Experience

2022-present

Front-End developer (I selected Web Development as my professional career & create some small Projects & do all my best to growing fast as I can)

2020-2021

lecturer in Chra Private institue

2020-2021

Assistant lecturer in Charmo University

Since 2020

Graphic Designer (logo design ,social media post ,branding ,poster ,brochure, business card ...)